Guide to the Robert Parmelee Wilder Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, Series V
  - Biographical Material
    - Clippings, articles, 1903-1908 (Box 24, Folder 224)
    - Clippings, articles, 1910-1913 (Box 24, Folder 225)
    - Clippings, articles, 1914-1919 (Box 24, Folder 226)
    - Clippings, articles, 1920-1924 (Box 24, Folder 227)
    - Clippings, articles, 1925-1933 (Box 24, Folder 228)
    - Clippings, articles, 1934-1937 (Box 24, Folder 229)
    - Clippings, articles, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - Clippings, articles, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - Clippings, articles, Autobiographical sketch, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1887-1909 (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1909-1912 (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1913-1916 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1920-1925 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, 1927-1935 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - Publicity notices, itineraries, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - Material gathered by Ruth Wilder Braisted, 1924-1939 Aug (Box 25, Folder 240)
    - Material gathered by Ruth Wilder Braisted, 1939 Sep-1940, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - Material gathered by Ruth Wilder Braisted, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - Photographs
    - Various, 1879-1928, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 243)
  - Miscellaneous personal items
    - Various, 1891-1939, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 244-245)